chefscatalog.com 2014-12-16

# CHEFS: The Best Kitchen Starts Here

At CHEFS Catalog, we want you to know how we collect, use, share and protect information about you. By interacting with CHEFScatalog.com, you consent to the use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically. To help you track the changes, we include a history of changes below.

CHEFS Catalog is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Target Corporation.

Types of personal information we collect include:

  * Your name 
  * Your mailing address 
  * Your e-mail address 
  * Your phone (or mobile) number 
  * Your drivers' license number 
  * Your credit/debit card number 
  * Your purchase/return/exchange information 
  * Your registry event information 
  * Your date of birth or age 
  * Your interests and product preferences 
  * Your friend’s names, e-mail addresses, and mailing addresses 
  * Messages you write when you send recipes, write reviews, ask questions or make comments 

If you choose not to provide personal information we may not be able to provide you with requested products, services or information. 

**Automated Information Collection**

_CHEFS Catalog Automated Collection_

We and our service providers use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website through your computer or mobile device. This information, which includes the pages you visit on our site, which web address you came from, the type of browser/device/hardware you are using, purchase information and checkout process, search terms and IP-based geographic location, helps us customize your website experience and make our marketing messages more relevant. This includes content presented on another website or mobile application.. These technologies enable us to provide features such as storage of items in your cart between visits, Short Message Service (SMS)/text messages you have chosen to receive, items previously viewed, to improve site design, product assortments, customer service, and provide promotions.

In order to provide the best guest experience possible, we also use these technologies for reporting and analysis purposes, such as how you are shopping our website, performance of our marketing efforts, and your response to those marketing efforts.

_Third-Party Automated Collection_

CHEFS Catalog participates in online behavioral advertising (OBA), also known as interest-based advertising. We use third-party advertising companies to display ads tailored to your individual interests based on how you browse and shop online.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our website and to use that information to serve ads for products or services or for the products or services of other companies when you visit this website or other websites. These companies use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, hardware/software information, MAC address, cookie and session ID, and personally identifiable information (e.g. IP address)) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These parties typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. 

At this time, we do not respond to browser “do not track” signals, but we do provide you the option to opt out of behavioral advertising. To learn more about OBA or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Social Media Widgets**

Chefscatalog.com includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, Google Plus, Pinterest, and Twitter widgets. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you’re visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

**Information from Other Sources**

We collect data that’s publicly available. For example, information you submit in a public forum (e.g. a blog, chat room, or social network) can be read, collected, or used by us and others, and could be used to personalize your experience. You are responsible for the information you choose to submit in these instances.

We also obtain information provided by third parties. For instance, we obtain information from companies that can enhance our existing guest information to improve the accuracy and add to the information we have about our guests (for example, adding address information).

This improves our ability to contact you and increases the relevance of our marketing by providing better product recommendations or special offers that may interest you. 

Examples of how we use the information we collect include:

**Product and Service Fulfillment**

  * Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, returns/exchanges, or requests for information about our products and services on our, website and mobile website, or to otherwise serve you 
  * Connect with us regarding guest service via our contact center, or on social media platforms 
  * Provide services such as wish list, Gift Registry or a saved cart 
  * Administer sweepstakes and contests 

**Our Marketing Purposes**

  * Deliver catalogs or other offerings by mail, coupons, mobile coupons, newsletters, receipt messages, e-mails, mobile messages, and social media notifications 
  * Provide interactive features of the website, such as product reviews and other information regarding products, services and promotions 

**Internal Operations**

  * Improve the effectiveness of our website and marketing efforts, merchandise selections, guest service, and overall shopping experience 
  * Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys 
  * Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy 

**Fraud Prevention**

  * To prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business (e.g. product recalls) 

**Legal Compliance**

  * For example, assist law enforcement and respond to legal/regulatory inquiries 

Target Corporation

We share the information we collect within Target Corporation, which includes all Target subsidiaries and affiliates.

Target Corporation may use this information to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you.

Target Corporation owns Target Stores and Target web sites. Target Corporation subsidiaries and affiliates include, but are not limited to: Target Bank, Target Canada, Target Commercial Interiors, TCC Cooking Co.(Cooking.com and CHEFS Catalog) and Dermstore LLC (Dermstore.com, Blush.com, Hairenvy.com).

**Service Providers**

We may share the information we collect with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, e-mail, mobile marketing, analytics providers, web hosting providers, call center service providers, sweepstakes vendors, payment processors, coupon delivery vendors, or data enhancement provider) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.

**Legal Requirements**

We may disclose information we collect when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply applicable terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our guests or others.

**Elsewhere at Your Direction**

At your direction or request, we may share your information. For example, if you create a wish list, gift registry or saved cart and elect to make it available to the public, your information will be accessible on our website, mobile or social applications, and in our stores.

**Sharing with Other Companies (for their marketing purposes)**

CHEFS Catalog may share your personal information with other companies, or organizations which are not part of CHEFS Catalog . These companies and organizations may use the information we share to provide special offers and opportunities to you. To opt out of our sharing of your personal information with such companies and organizations go to the Choice section of this privacy policy.

**Sharing Aggregate Information with Third Parties**

We may share aggregate information (information that does not directly identify an individual) with third parties for lawful purposes.

**Business Transfers**

If some or all of our business assets are sold or transferred, we may transfer the corresponding information regarding our guests. We also may retain a copy of that guest information.

**Postal Mail**

If you do not wish to receive catalogs, coupons, and other promotional mail, contact us:

  * **By email:** customerservice@ecare.chefscatalog.com 
  * **By Phone.** Call toll-free at (800) 338-3232 or 
  * **By postal mail.** Please mail request to us at: CHEFS Management, 5070 Centennial Blvd., Colorado Springs, CO 80919 

**Email**

Upon ordering or creating an account at chefscatalog.com, you will receive promotional e-mails from CHEFS. You always have the ability to "opt-out" or stop receiving promotional e-mails from CHEFS by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email, logging into your account and managing your preferences, or contacting customer service at 800-338-3232 or customerservice@ecare.chefscatalog.com.

**If you choose to "opt-out," we will stop sending you promotional e-mails, but will still send you order confirmations and shipping notice emails.**

**Sharing with Other Companies (for their marketing purposes)**

If you do not want CHEFS Catalog to share information about you with other companies (for their marketing purposes) contact us:

  * **By email:** customerservice@ecare.chefscatalog.com 
  * **By Phone.** Call toll-free at (800) 338-3232 or 
  * **By postal mail.** Please mail request to us at: CHEFS Management, 5070 Centennial Blvd., Colorado Springs, CO 80919 

**Third Party Cookies**

To opt out of third-party cookies, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**California Residents**

If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with CHEFS Catalog you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information shared with third parties, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to:

CHEFS Management  
Attn: California Shine the Light Inquiry  
5070 Centennial Blvd.  
Colorado Springs, CO 80919

Please allow 30 days for a response.

In order to keep your personal information accurate and complete, you can access or update some of it in the following ways: 

If you have created a CHEFS Catalog account, you can log in and update your account information, including contact, billing, and shipping information.

Contact us with your current contact information and the personal information you would like to access. We will provide you the personal information requested if reasonably available, or will describe the types of personal information we typically collect.

Write to:

CHEFS Management  
5070 Centennial Blvd.  
Colorado Springs, CO 80919

**Security Methods**

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect your personal information. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit or debit card number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. However, no e-commerce solution, website, database or system is completely secure or “hacker proof.” You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse.

**E-mail Security**

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through e-mail.

**Children’s Personal Information**

We recognize the particular importance of protecting privacy where children are involved. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information online, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us or call 800-338-3232.

**Mail:**

CHEFS Management  
5070 Centennial Blvd.  
Colorado Springs, CO 80919

**Phone:**

800-338-3232

**E-mail:**

customerservice@ecare.chefscatalog.com

**Last update: 1/28/2014**  
January 2014 Added Dermstore LLC websites to the list of subsidiaries and affiliates
